[Music]
sup everyone came with a five here with
the very first developer's update for my
video game the ledger a prophecy of
light and darkness the power to save the
world in the developers update I'll be
showing you many things from a bit of
gameplay to the how the mechanics work
within my game first off as you can say
you use the arrow keys to walk around
you use spacebar to interact with the
objects like so I love apples my book
from bumble bee owns an apple tree so I
get fresh ones every day I have to sneak
them into our bedroom to eat them though
uncle chip gets angled we eat food
without permission even if it is given
to us now as you can see this right here
is a playable character saying now if
you press the X button you can bring up
the menu on this side of the screen will
be your party as you can see right now
saying it is all in the only kitchen
Authority and your subtitle is here
because he is the hero of our story he
is killing level 1 and we got 0 gold the
reason of this is because we are still
at the beginning of the game over here
you can see many other things such as
your items skills equips status
formation options save and game and
right now the menu isn't all the flesh
out but in due time I will be however if
you go skill and look at talk skills you
can see that right now
no stew erase heal and spa then not only
can you interact with objects in the
overworld
but you can also interact with other
characters this green man right here is
named the man he is sentenced twin rova
warning saying you aged potatoes it's
almost sunrise the man
I'm not picking taters today bro don't
say that so loud you don't want to chip
to get mad at you I'm serious bro I
don't care uncle chip hears me he needs
to know the way he treats us his
family now as you can probably tell the
story is gonna be pretty damn deep
if you're wondering what by the
way if you're wondering why I'm filming
with the camera it's because Mac appear
kind of sucks boss so I can find any
girl according to some week to record
the game without my computer lagging now
over here we can see swooping around
if we talk to a dis is Stephanie
hey Stephanie you're up oh well yeah I
gotta get to what kind of tell you this
last week I've got to count them and
uncle Chet B miles like steel-drum I saw
so don't want that again now over the
course of the game you'll be writing to
many people not just your sibs and
shared but many people who will be
coming with you longer right along the
way now this is this is just begin the
game however to continue the story we
will go here go down as you could see in
on our cuts and you'll be pulled into a
cutscene well today's a day the day that
we begin our families freedom bro away
yeah you're not going to fire without us
are you Oh looks like the man said you
are coming with us
that's cool the more manpower as you can
see we are heading that's just you go
Bianca tips act now as you can see right
here there are other pathways however of
course
Nachi you cannot leave until your
objectives finish and an objective right
now is to take down uncle chug
uncle chair now and you can see uncle
chip is walking right now we can't let
that we got a beats and ass well if
isn't my three little I'll see
y'all killing any taters and just about
stand it's just about sunrise that means
y'all about tennis late for when you're
supposed to begin harvesting do you live
boys and girls need a spanking as
punishment you should shut the up
or man yeah you're not going to be
treating us as your cute little
any longer what do you just say Punk now
you'll be able to see be able to see
more of the conversation when you play
the game itself now for now I'll be
skipping straight to the striking of
being in the battle as you can see once
the battle began tough playing each
other so this is this is a song for the
football cause you can see
thankful for us to attack who we will
hit the spacebar does uncle chip the
male attacking kid again attack and you
continue to give it damage and she took
us down this is we would nothing
however as you can see this wasn't
unwinnable battle one thing that my game
makes it unique is some Bells are just
out rods unwinnable and when this
happens I guess you gotta you just gotta
move on it's demon - as you can see
I'll go check carry this over to the
waterfall
Tim's begging um and he throws he jet he
just grabs singing by the ass and close
him off the water bro no bro
say bandits is visiting wow that's fun I
think if you wanted to stop by my Silvia
what's gonna happen
what's this it was on that day that my
best friend my life on the hold of my
heart
say saying my love is that you as you
can see the prologue has ended and this
is will your story will begin when you
buy my game peace out
this has been the end of the first
developers update I hope you enjoy my
fun my kickstart will be up soon I
really hope that your project if
this looks good to you your final
project and we can and we can make this
the best game ever game of 2018 whoa
let's go